[guitar music playing]
[Mickey] Dude, this house is insane.
[Gus] Oh, it's fucking nuts, right?
-[Mickey] Fucking nuts.
-Yeah.
Wow.
[chuckles] Wow.
[Gus] Gordon! Peanut!
Oh, there they are.
Oh, there's a Gordon and Peanut!
[in baby talk] There's a Gordon
and a little Peanut. Hi.
Mickey, this is Gordon. This is Peanut.
Peanut, Gordon, this is Mickey.
-Oh. Hi, Gordon and Peanut.
-Give me kisses.
Aw, who are these goofballs?
Who are these goofballs?
Gus, this house is incredible.
Just leave the dogs. Show me around.
-Okay.
-[elevator bell dings]
[chuckles] Well, the elevator works.
Yep. This is nuts.
Wow.
[Mickey chuckles softly]
-This kitchen.
-It's insane.
What's that?
-Uh, a fridge.
-No.
Old-timey fridge.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Oh, my God!
-[sing-song] Ah!
This is all original.
-Wow.
-Nice. Yeah.
-Oh, my God.
-Mmm-hmm.
-This bedroom's amazing.
-Yeah.
What's in here?
Oh, my God.
She has, like, a million pairs of shoes.
Gus, how many shoes can I steal?
So being a kid actor
can get you a house like this?
Mmm, no.
He just comes from a really rich family
and invested well.
Oh. So like...
everyone I knew in New York.
Mmm-hmm. Now he's married,
so, uh, when he goes out of town,
he just... just asks me to house-sit.
-Mmm.
-Yeah.
This is gonna be such an awesome way
to watch Witchita tomorrow, you know?
Mmm.
Are you flipping out?
You must be flipping out.
-I am.
-[high-pitched] Yeah?
I think my parents are more.
My mom drug out all
the Halloween decorations from the garage
and put 'em at the house
so they'd have witch stuff everywhere.
[clicks tongues] Aw.
Wanna fuck outside?
[both breathing heavily]
[both moaning]
[theme music playing]
[Mickey] Oh, my God.
If Shaun posts one more photo
of her baby wearing sunglasses,
I am unfollowing her for life.
Oh, my God.
I love hearing you shit-talk your friends.
Why?
'Cause it makes me know you, like,
really trust me, you know?
Don't flatter yourself.
I'll shit-talk to anyone who will listen.
Oh. [sniffles]
-Okay, I know this is gross, but...
-Ooh.
Can I please pop a zit on your back?
[inhales sharply] Uh, ugh...
All right,
if you think it's gross, I won't.
No, no. I don't think it's gross.
I think, like, I'm gross.
I'm just, like, self-conscious
about my zits and stuff, so I feel--
Are you kidding me? Popping pimples
is my favorite thing in life.
-[inhales deeply] Okay.
-Thank you.
-Go for it.
-Thank you so much.
-Oh, my God.
-Okay.
-One... two...
-[inhales sharply]
-Did you get it?
-Yes.
[groans]
-Look at it.
-Mmm-mmm.
-Thank you for letting me be gross.
-You're welcome.
You know, I can talk shit with anyone,
but popping someone's pimples...
[dog barking]
[Gus clicks tongue]
[groans] I should probably
go walk those dogs.
[Mickey] Who else lives around here?
Any celebrities that haven't
been dead for 500 years?
[chuckles] Uh... I think I heard
Matthew Perry lives around here.
-Cool.
-Maybe. Yeah.
[gasps] So that could mean that
that is Matthew Perry's personal trainer.
[Gus] Oh, yeah.
Oh, you know Matthew Perry
is in cooldown mode right now.
[chuckles]
All right.
Ooh, I think Gordon has to poopie.
Oh, okay.
It's kind of weird
seeing you smoke out here, you know?
'Cause this neighborhood's so fancy.
Feels like it's like
one big non-smoking section, you know?
Okay.
What?
I don't know,
that just seemed a little, uh... judge-y.
Do you hate that I smoke?
-Why? Do you want me to hate it?
-Do I want you to hate it?
Like, if it'd help you to quit,
knowing that I hated it or something.
I mean, are you...
Are you trying to quit or is that not...
I just noticed you've been, like,
smoking more than you did before.
I've been smoking more
because I'm in AA and SLAA,
and I cannot give up anything else,
like, for the rest of my life.
No. Totally, totally, totally.
I get it. Yeah.
I wasn't trying to shame you
or whatever, you know.
I know you're rockin' it.
I'm super proud of you.
Okay.
That a boy, Gordon.
Hmm.
I put the dogs in their special room,
so they're good for the night.
Cool. Hmm. Lookin' at these photo albums,
I feel like I know these people on, like,
a psychological level.
Oh, yeah? Do tell.
He hates his parents.
-That's obvious.
-Mmm-hmm.
They got married too young,
but they've got a great sex life.
-I think that's 100% right.
-[both chuckle]
[stammers] Are you wearing new pajamas?
Uh, kind of. I got 'em from that drawer.
You're wearing Linda's pajamas?
Well, we're in Linda's house,
sleeping in Linda's bed.
Might as well wear Linda's pajamas, right?
Yeah, cool with me.
How much do you think
a house like this is worth?
Ooh, I don't know.
I'm bad with that stuff.
-Maybe, like, $200.
-Hmm.
-[chuckles]
-I think, like, five to seven million.
-Probably. That's crazy, huh?
-Yeah.
I've always wanted
to live in a house like this.
It's the dream, to be honest.
-Is that lame?
-No, it's not lame to have a dream.
Dreams are good.
Dreams make people, you know,
work hard to earn the things they want.
I don't wanna earn it.
I just wanna have it.
[chuckles] Yeah, but how would you buy it?
Marry some rich dude.
Some guy that's about to die
and gives me all his money.
Don't you think that's a little...
anti-feminist?
Shouldn't a woman want to go out
in the world and...
not depend on some other guy for--
Are you explaining feminism
to me right now? Is that what's happening?
Never mind.
I'm not gonna say anything more.
I just want to have a relaxed life.
Always have.
Live in a big house, read some books
and have a cat. Is that so wrong?
No. It's perfect.
That's a perfect dream. I... I love that.
[chuckles] But, honestly, how...
how often do you think that happens?
Like, really happens?
-Women marrying old men for money?
-Yeah.
Every 15 seconds.
No.
Mmm. You think that Jerry Hall
married Rupert Murdoch
because she loves him?
Yeah, I believe she loves him.
He's living on borrowed time
and she knows it.
-He's probably a cool guy.
-Uh-huh.
He's, like, smart, charming, witty.
Okay, you're making
a pro-Rupert Murdoch argument right now.
I'm just saying we should
give more credit to these wives.
Like, did you see those pictures of them
on the wedding day?
They looked very happy.
I'd rather see the photos of them
on the wedding night.
-That's when the work starts.
-Mnh-mnh.
Jesus Lord. Choking down that dick?
Please, she earned every cent.
You know...
if Rupert Murdoch didn't exist,
there wouldn't be The Simpsons.
I'm willing to live with that.
Wow.
-Do you mind if I watch TV?
-No, it'll help me fall asleep.
Fucking awesome. Okay.
All right. Here we go. [grunts]
[TV playing indistinctly]
Fuck.
Mickey!
Hey, Mickey, can you come here?
[Mickey] Sure!
-What's up?
-Hey, uh, did you let one of the dogs in?
Oh, yeah. I was bored,
so I let Peanut in to keep me company.
Mmm, okay.
'Cause you know we're supposed to
keep an eye on the dogs if they're inside.
Remember, that's, like, one of the...
The rules?
-Yeah.
Well, um, Peanut pooped in the house.
[groans]
-I'm sorry. Where?
-[stammers] Here.
[groans] Okay, I'll clean it up.
It won't leave a stain.
Not so much a stain
that I'm worried about, it's more, like...
When a dog poops,
it's marking its territory.
So now every time he poops,
he's gonna wanna poop here--
Okay, can you not say poop?
Just say shit or--
Okay. Poop. Shit. Fuck. Turds.
Whatever, okay? He took a shit,
and it wouldn't have happened
if you had looked and paid attention.
-I'm sorry.
-I'll clean it up.
Just can you take the dogs outside
or something, please? For me.
Yeah, I have to smoke anyway.
Peanut! Gordon!
[softly] Okay.
[doorbell rings]
-Hi!
-Hey!
-[Mickey] Syd!
-Mickey!
-[Jeff] Hey.
-[Mickey and Syd] Oh!
-[Mickey] You remember Gus.
-[Syd] Hi, Gus.
-This is Jeff, my husband.
-Hi, welcome!
-Hey. [chuckles]
-[Gus chuckles]
-Hi, welcome. [chuckles]
-Oh, hello.
Ooh, sorry. [chuckles]
[Syd] Oh, God.
Are we the first ones here?
Please tell me we're not that lame.
-[Mickey] You're the first ones here.
-Fuck.
Hey, come on. Don't worry.
You don't think I've been
in this position before? It's no problem.
The babysitter showed up, so we're like,
"Hey, let's get outta here."
And then, you know, Syd and I don't do
a lot of stuff at night,
so we got excited.
We bolted out of the fucking house.
-Yeah.
-[Gus chuckles]
Hey, Syd, come check out the backyard.
-Yeah.
-[Mickey] Yeah.
[Jeff and Gus chuckle]
-Wow, this is cool.
-It is, isn't it?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, yeah.
So I slam on my brakes going, like,
60 miles an hour.
Otis is in the backseat
barfing up frozen yogurt...
-Oh, my God.
-and I just miss rear-ending this guy.
Ugh, I almost hit an office chair
on the freeway once,
and it traumatized me for, like, a year.
Are you gonna get in trouble with Jeff
if he sees you smoking that?
No, he'll be cool with it.
He usually is when we go out.
That way I can't judge him
for whatever he does.
-Yeah.
-What about Gus? He cool with it?
Oh, he asked me yesterday
if I ever thought about quitting.
-You didn't like that.
-I mean, I like Gus.
I like him, but sometimes I feel like
I'm his fixer-upper or something.
-Yeah?
-I don't know.
We went to lunch with my dad
the other week,
and he was really nice and supportive,
but it also felt like he was getting off
on watching me be damaged, too, you know?
Or, just devil's advocating here,
maybe he really is supportive and caring.
But he's kinda condescending about it,
you know? It's the way he does it.
And I know if I ever messed up,
he would be so disappointed in me.
[stammers] It's too much pressure.
I wouldn't worry about it.
I think you're just feeling this way
because you guys have been cooped up
in this house together.
If he goes, "I'm proud of you,"
one more time,
I'm gonna slit his fucking throat.
[Jeff] So, you guys know Mickey?
-Yeah.
Great. How do you know her?
-I work with her at the radio station.
-Oh, cool.
How about you?
Yeah, I work at the radio station, too.
Oh, so you're coworkers?
He doesn't work
at the radio station. [chuckling]
-Nah, I was just being an asshole.
-Oh.
-I don't even fucking know this guy.
-[all laugh]
-I don't know him either, no.
-Are you guys fucking with me?
[both] No.
-Oh, wow.
-What's your name again?
-Len.
-Truman. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
So what about you?
Uh, you've been dating anybody?
Nah. Do you know what's crazy, dude?
I've been hooking up with an ex.
Ever since Witchita ended,
I need something stable in my life.
-Oh, totally. I hear that. Yeah.
-Yeah, so what about you?
Is Mickey staying with you this whole time
you've been in this dump?
Yeah, she was here, uh, last night
and then tonight and tomorrow night.
-Three nights?
-Mmm-hmm.
Three nights? That's what happens
when you're not working.
You fill up your free time
with your dick.
No, it's okay, 'cause, you know,
I'm going out of town pretty soon
-to do that movie with Arya.
-Uh-huh.
So, just trying to get in
some quality time before I go.
Slow down, slow down.
How long have you been talking
to this girl?
I don't know, like, a month...
A little over a month.
Yeah, dude, a little over a month
but you're treating it
like it's been two years.
Relax, bro. Relax.
I'm pretty sure Mickey's a nice girl,
but she seems a bit... complex.
See, that's what I like about her,
that she is complex, you know?
It's like every day,
I learn a little bit more about her,
and I think I start to understand her,
then she does something that just, like...
I don't know. I love it.
She's like a puzzle, and I love puzzles.
I like a nice 24-piece puzzle.
-Mickey's like a 500-piece puzzle.
-Well...
Anyway, I'm glad you're here.
We get to celebrate the end
of Witchita together, huh?
-Yes, yes, yes. RIP Witchita, man.
-Yes.
Hey, buddy,
I'm so sorry about that tattoo.
Dude, I'm not there yet.
[indistinct chatter]
So you two are Mickey's friends?
Uh, yeah.
I've known Mickey since forever.
[Chris] Cool.
What about you guys?
Are you Mickey's friends?
-We're Gus' friends.
-I'm his best friend.
I only ask because
I never know who Mickey's friends are.
Seems like
she's always making new friends.
Why do you say that like it's a bad thing?
Well, I think people get to know
Mickey's bullshit,
-and she has to make new friends.
-Where is she, anyways?
Like, I feel like I never see her.
Let me guess.
Upstairs, fucking some random dude.
[Shaun] Okay, shut up.
You're done talking now.
-I'm done talking now.
-Yeah.
Like, I've been in two fights
in my lifetime.
What about you, man?
Me? None. Uh, never. I've never... fight.
What about you, Stretch?
-[clicks tongue] About a dozen.
-What?
When I see injustice, I fight.
-Did you say your name was Alexis?
-Yeah.
You look super familiar.
Are you on Tinder?
Maybe.
Jesus. What the hell am I doing here?
Da-da-da-dah. Ooh!
Oh, you look good.
Thank you.
This Linda woman has good taste.
Yeah.
So, hey, um,
did you invite Randy tonight or...
-Uh, no. I assumed you'd tell him.
-Okay, gotcha.
-Did you? Did you tell him?
-[chuckles] Uh, no. But that's okay.
Okay.
So do you think
Gus could have maybe invited him?
-I don't know. Why? What's going on?
-Nothing. It's just...
I guess things have been a little bit
strained between Randy and I lately,
so... if he doesn't come tonight,
that's okay.
-Okay.
-But I love all these jewels.
I feel so regal, like the kind of woman
who's probably great at dinner parties,
but is a bit racist.
-What time is it?
-Oh, just after 8:30.
Oh, I gotta get everybody
gathered around the TV for Witchita.
You ready for some Witchita,
motherfuckers?
[all cheering]
Yeah, and keep it going
for the man of the hour, Gus Cruikshank!
[all cheering]
Thank you. Thank you.
All right, DVR-ed
for zero commercial interruption.
Five...
[all] Four, three, two, one...
[all cheering]
[Witchita theme music playing on TV]
[church bell tolling on TV]
[Elise] It really is a beautiful steeple,
Reverend.
-[Pastor Lewis] Hmm. Yes.
-[all cheering]
-[Mickey chuckles] "Story by"!
-[Gus] Yeah. Wow, wow, wow.
You know,
you should join me here this evening.
Oh, uh, of course, Reverend.
Yeah, Heidi. Go hook up with Pastor Lewis
and stay off of Gus' dick.
-[Chris laughs]
-Ha. Very funny, very funny.
Yeah, Heidi.
Why don't you stay off Gus' dick?
[chuckles]
[laughing nervously] Oh, boy.
[Elise] It's just that my mother died...
-[softly] Why'd you say that?
-[whispers] It's a joke.
Yeah. No, that's... that's funny.
[Chris] Is she a witch? Gus.
-What?
-Who is witches? Like, is...
-She is? She's a witch?
-Yeah, they're all...
-Most of them are witches.
-Oh, okay.
-Witchita.
-[chuckles]
-Do you get it? Yeah.
-[laughing] Yeah.
Hello? Mickey?
-Oh, my God, Andy. Sorry.
-[Andy] Echo!
[Mickey] All right. Sorry. Hi!
-Hi, how are you?
-Hi. Good.
-Sorry, you guys.
-Uh, this is my friend, Andy.
It's Andy Dick, obviously.
-[woman] Hi.
-Uh, spoiler alert,
Colonel Mustard is giving it
to Miss Scarlet up in the conservatory
with the candlestick right now. [chuckles]
-What's going on?
-Listen, can I talk to you?
-Yeah.
-In private.
-What's up?
-AA stuff.
-[whispers indistinctly]
-Yep. Yeah.
Sorry. Enjoy.
Um... I just gotta go talk to Andy
about some AA stuff,
so do you want to pause the episode
or is that, like, annoying for people?
Uh, yeah,
I guess we'll just keep it running
but come back as soon as you can.
-Yeah.
-Okay.
[giggles] I bet you can see
the whole town from up here.
Oh, look, there's Jarvis. Jarvis!
I had the, um, initial audition...
-Uh-huh.
-and I fuckin' killed it.
I really did.
Even I was like, "Fuck," you know.
Because I've been saying no to all...
About five auditions all year.
-Because they're triggers for me.
-Yeah.
They're triggers.
I... I used to drink...
before I would audition and, um--
When's the last time
you went in sober to an audition?
Nineteen...
Never.
I just feel like
death follows me wherever I go.
All of these murders in town,
it's giving me a fright.
[Pastor Lewis] My dear. My dear.
Now is the time...
-to hold our friends very close.
-[cell phone vibrating]
You know, you never really know
who to trust these days.
What the fuck, Bertie?
Why are you texting me, "I'm outside"?
Just come inside. We're watching Witchita.
I'm not going in because you obviously
don't want me to be in there.
No, I just... I'm sorry, I forgot.
Gus texted me, "Why aren't you here?"
I had no idea what he was talking about.
I had to ask him, like some sort of loser.
Like, my girlfriend and all my friends
are watching TV in a big mansion,
and I'm not invited to come in?
[sighs] It just made me feel really sad.
And I feel like
you're being weird to me and...
No, I'm not. It's just...
Just come inside.
I... I missed you.
Aw...
I missed you, too.
Do you think they noticed I wasn't here?
Should we say I had,
like, a flat tire or something?
No. No one cares. It's fine.
I mean, now, he's, like,
so into my sobriety
that it's kind of borderline creepy--
-Oh, God, I hate that.
-Right? He's, like, trying to, like--
Well, welcome to my world.
-Well--
-The whole world's into my sobriety.
I know.
I can't even imagine what that feels like.
Can't stand it.
So now he's, like, keeping track of me.
I feel like he's got a chart
in his apartment
where it's like,
"number of meetings per week."
I'm... I'm barely exaggerating.
Oh, yeah, but you know what?
God, I wish I had something like that.
-No, Andy.
-What?
-No, we're never gonna make out.
-Don't... Please don't say "never."
[Pastor Lewis] Oh, no, no, Detective.
I've never seen anything like it either.
Hmm. Uh, let's see, well, Wednesdays?
Wednesdays, we minister to the poor...
-[whispering] Are you farting?
-[whispering] No.
Yes, you are.
I can smell it, Jeff. It's disgusting.
Well, if you know it's me, why do you ask?
[sighs]
[Pastor Lewis] Her memory's
a little spotty these days
due to her advanced age and all.
But, uh, I'm sure she'll vouch for me
and verify my whereabouts. [chuckles]
Hey. Hey, Len.
Can you take the glass of wine
off the floor?
-I just... I don't want it to spill.
-Yeah, no problem.
[Elise] They really are stunning at night.
Okay, thanks.
[Pastor Lewis] Yes, it is lovely, my dear.
-Say good night... forever!
-[Elise screams]
[thud]
Oh, my God. That lady fell.
-Someone get help!
-[all chuckling]
Fuck.
[stammering] Um, Gus, sorry.
I think one of the dogs ate chocolate.
They're acting all sick.
They're barfing. They're gonna barf more.
Are you serious? Did somebody
open the door to the dog room?
-[bottle clatters]
-God...
-[Len] Sorry.
-Fuck!
-Hey, it's okay, buddy. We'll clean up.
-[Gus] It's okay. Uh...
I'm gonna take care of this.
-Where they at? Is it Gordon?
-I don't know. They look the same.
Do we have to keep watching?
'Cause it's... I can't.
We have to go, actually,
'cause we have a sitter.
-Okay, guys.
-[indistinct chatter]
[Shaun] Nice to see you. Bye.
Bye. So good to see you guys.
-[Andy speaking indistinctly]
-[Mickey] Okay. Call me tomorrow.
Okay. And... and thanks.
Probably call you tonight.
-Okay. Bye.
-Okay. Thank you.
[door opens and closes]
Oh, did everybody leave?
Yeah.
Well, you were up there a long time.
-So...
-Oh. Yeah.
Gordon ate some chocolate, but I helped
him puke it up, so he's okay now.
All right.
So, why are you cleaning now?
Just leave it for tomorrow.
-Because I want to clean up now.
-Wow, you're so anal.
Mickey, if I wanna clean up,
I can clean up. All right?
God forbid I have respect
for other people's stuff, right?
Wow.
Is this what you're like?
If we lived together,
would you be like this?
Like, get all wound up
when things are messy?
Why are you picking a fight
with me right now?
-You should be the one who's apologizing.
-For what?
For missing my episode!
Like, ten minutes in, you just stand up
and, like, walk out of the room
and don't see any of it.
Yeah, 'cause I had to talk to Andy.
Okay, first of all...
you're friends with Andy Dick?
What the fuck?
And then, second of all...
I guess Andy Dick is more important
than my episode of Witchita, huh?
He had to talk to me
about some deeply personal shit
and he needed to talk
to someone in the program
and that is way more important
than your stupid
little episode of television
that you just want
everybody to suck your dick about.
Wow. You are jealous.
It's like you couldn't even
be there for me
when something good was happening.
What was good?
Are you talking about Witchita?
-That show fucking sucks.
-Okay, don't say that.
You say that all the time!
Yeah, I can say it, but you can't.
Just support me!
Oh, so lie to you now?
Okay, it was great.
All right, yeah.
Whatever, Mickey. Fine.
I'm an asshole because I wanted
you to watch my show with me, okay?
Ugh, [sighs] just... Okay, just...
Please just stop monitoring me, okay?
-What?
-You monitor me all the time!
I do not monitor you.
You suffocate me.
I have no personal space.
You're, like, keeping tallies
on me all the time.
Like, four meetings this week,
three meetings last week,
and you're fucking, like,
checking up on me.
You know what?
Why don't you go find some rich old guy,
-and you can be his kept woman...
-[scoffs]
and he can fucking ignore you,
which is what you want.
You don't want anybody caring about you,
you don't want anybody
looking out for you.
You wanted to be treated
like dirt and be ignored,
'cause that's what you're familiar with.
And then somebody comes along
and treats you kindly,
and you don't know
how to fucking process it!
Wow. That's nice.
That's real fucking rude of you.
-Where are my cigarettes? Where--
-Why would I know?
-Did you fucking hide my cigarettes?
-Oh, my God.
Yes, Mickey, I took your cigarettes
and I hid them from you. You got me.
You act like it's a joke,
but I wouldn't put it past you.
I'm sure that's something
you'd love to do.
You're accusing me of hiding cigarettes?
-You keep tabs on me--
-That's so fucking bonkers!
You wanna fucking monitor me?
Fine, watch this. Monitor this.
Jesus Christ!
[sighs]
[water running]
Hey, Gus.
Oh. Hey.
Hey, what's up, man?
Uh, I hope you don't mind,
I crashed here last night.
Oh! That's okay. It's cool.
I'm getting ready
to get out of here right now.
-Good morning.
-Good...
-[Alexis] Hey.
-Hey, how's everything?
Can I get a ride?
-Where you... Where you headed?
-Westside.
Damn, I live in North Hollywood.
-So?
-You know what, I...
We'll figure this out outside, man.
Crazy party once again.
Uh, I'll see you, bro.
All right. Bye.
-Great Witchita.
-Thank you. Bye-bye.
[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
-Hey.
-What's up? Are you taking off?
-Yeah.
I figured, let you take care of the house
-for the last night.
-Oh.
Okay.
-Hey, I'm sorry about last night.
-No, I'm sorry.
We were getting along
and then I started acting out and...
[sighs] I don't know.
Well, let's leave together. Huh?
I'll just pack my stuff up
and we can take off and--
Stay here.
We can have lunch tomorrow.
Enjoy the house, you know.
Watch a movie on the big TV.
Avatar or something.
Okay.
So, uh, yeah, we'll just...
We'll talk tomorrow.
Yeah.
Okay.
Um... [sighs]
I'm sorry about the crystal bowl.
I'll buy a new one.
Yeah. I looked online and...
-one of those costs $2,000.
-Oh.
Okay. In that case...
maybe we could pretend
like nothing happened
and see if anyone notices?
That's my whole philosophy
in life. [chuckles]
-[inhales deeply] Okay.
-Okay.
Right. [sighs]
[Eel's "Love of the Loveless" playing]
♪ Don't got a lot of time ♪
♪ Don't give a damn ♪
♪ Don't tell me what to do ♪
♪ I am the man ♪
♪ If there's a God up there ♪
♪ Something above ♪
♪ God, shine your light down here ♪
♪ Shine on the love
Love of the loveless ♪
♪ Love of the loveless ♪
♪ Don't have too many friends
Never felt at home ♪
♪ Always been my own man
Pretty much alone ♪
♪ I know how to get through ♪
♪ And when push comes to shove ♪
♪ I got something that you need ♪
♪ I got the love ♪
♪ Love of the loveless ♪
♪ The love of the loveless ♪